pixelofink.com 2015-11-01

# Privacy Policy | Pixel of Ink

:: Commitment to Privacy

Pixel of Ink is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should I ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Pixel of Ink reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. I will promptly reflect any such modifications in these Web pages.

:: Use of Cookies

Pixel of Ink may use cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences or other information that visitors send via their browser. Some of my advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on my site. My advertising partners include, but are not limited to, Google Adsense, and Amazon.com. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Pixel of Ink has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt out of certain practices. Pixel of Ink’s privacy policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

:: Information Collection

There are occasions when I will ask for personal information, such as when you enter a contest. In these cases, I will only collect personally identifiable information (such as name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) that you voluntarily provide through my Website or via email correspondence.

I will not sell or exchange your personal information at any time. I will collect general information (such as the type of browser you use, the files you request, and the domain name and country from which you request information) to improve my Website and better meet your needs.

:: Use of Information

Before I collect any personally identifiable information, I will provide an explanation for the possible use of your data. For example, the information you supply might be used by Pixel of Ink to respond to your inquiries or supply you with requested information. It may be necessary, if required by law or if pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations, to release your personally identifiable information. If you have submitted personal information to me electronically and would like it removed or modified, please contact me. I will use every possible reasonable effort to comply with your request.

:: Links

While Pixel of Ink is highly selective about which sites I provide links to, I do not control these web sites, nor do I endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. I encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on third party sites.

### Comments

comments
